Let us know with Mr. Policy
how you can change or update your policy details in ICICI LBD app.
First of all
install ICICI LBD mobile app from Google Play Store or Apple App Store.
After installation,
log in with your registered mobile number.
While logging in, enter the OTP
which you will receive on message or mail.
After logging in, you will
see the option of Policies in the home screen.  Click on it.
After this the option of edit policy details will
appear.  Click on it.  Then the
option of customer details will appear.
Click on it.  Now you
can update the details given below.  How to provide address, mobile number,
email ID, endorsements?   For
example, if you want to change your address,
enter your updated address.
Upload the relevant documents.
Like updated Aadhar card, Voter ID
card, Passport.  Then
after entering the reason for changing the address, click on Submit Request.
You will also receive endorsement updates on your registered email ID and
mobile app.  You can change
other details by repeating this process.
Keep these things in mind before changing the details.
Only one member's details can be updated at a time.
Changing the address or DOB
may require extra premium.  If you have any query then you
can comment.  Don't forget to follow
Mr. Policy for more informative videos related to insurance.